Let's see how we can communicate findings
لنرى كيف يمكننا توصيل النتائج
using visualizations with the census income data.
باستخدام مؤثرات العرض مع census income data.
Let's create two data frames to separate people who make above and below $50000.
لننشئ اثنين من إطارات البيانات لفصل الناس التي تجني أكثر من وأقل من 50000 دولار.
We can use bar graphs to compare the education levels reached in both groups.
يمكننا استخدام مخططات شريطية للمقارنة بين المستويات التعليمية التي وصل إليها المجموعتين.
Since value counts returns the counts in order by size,
بما أن أعداد القيمة تُعيد الأعداد بالترتيب حسب الحجم،
we don't have consistent x-axis labels for these graphs.
ليس لدينا ملصقات محور x متناسق لهذه الرسومات البيانية.
It's ideal to have the labels in the same order if we want to make a clear comparison.
من المثالي أن تكون الملصقات بنفس الترتيب إذا أردت إجراء مقارنة واضحة.
Let's order both results from value counts with the same index.
لنرتب النتيجتين من أعداد القيمة بنفس الفهرس.
That's much better.
هذا أفضل بكثير.
Next, let's plot pie charts to compare what work classes dominate in each group.
ثم بعد ذلك، لنرسم مخطط دائري مجزأ لمقارنة أي فئات العمل لها النصيب الأكبر في كل مجموعة.
Let's use the same indexing technique to keep the order of both results consistent.
لنستخدم نفس اسلوب الفهرسة لإبقاء ترتيب كلا النتائج متناسقًا.
Lastly, let's use histograms to plot the distribution of ages for each group.
وأخيرًا، لنستخدم مدرج تكراري لرسم توزيع الأعمار لكل مجموعة.
Interesting, the people who make more than 50000 seem to be older.
من المثير للاهتمام أن الأشخاص التي تجني أكثر من 50000 دولار هم الأكبر سنًا.
If we look at the summary statistics,
وإذا نظرنا إلى ملخص الإحصائيات،
we can see that the mean age for those making less is about 37,
يمكننا ان نرى أن متوسط أعمار من يجنون أقل هو حوالي 37 عام،
and 44 for those making more.
و 44 عام لمن يجنون أكثر.
This shows us that people making more are generally older but
يوضح لنا ذلك أن الأشخاص الذين يجنون أكثر هم بشكل عام الأكبر سنًا لكن
these visualizations give us
تعطينا مؤثرات العرض هذه
a much better idea of how those ages are distributed in these examples.
فكرة أفضل بكثير عن كيفية توزيع هذه الأعمار في هذه الامثلة.